Did you know that the missing Flight 19 reappears intact, year after year?
On December 5, 1945, five TBM Avenger torpedo bombers vanished over the Bermuda Triangle,
never to be seen until strange appearances began to occur.
Decades later, reports emerged of an intact Flight 19 suddenly appearing in remote
airstrips across the globe, briefly, eerily intact.
Each year, various locations from Argentina to Alaska report unconfirmed sightings
of these aircraft gliding through ghostly fogs, herald in calamity.
Authorities find nothing, leaving only chilled witnesses.
The pattern continues, leaving investigators puzzled as the planes
vanished just as they appeared, leaving behind only questions.